<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid19</string>
    <string name="general">Coronaviruses (CoV) are a large family of viruses that cause illness ranging from the common cold to more serious diseases such as Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS-CoV). The 2019 novel coronavirus is a new strain that has not been seen in humans until now and has caused viral pneumonia. It was first linked to Wuhan’s South China Seafood City market which is a wholesale market for seafood and live animals in December 2019. The virus has now been detected in several areas throughout China, along with countries across Asia, North and South America, Europe, Africa and Oceana.</string>
    <string name="symptoms">The most common symptoms: Fever dry cough Exhaustion Less common symptoms: Pains and aches Sore throat Diarrhea conjunctivitis a headache Loss of sense of taste or smell A rash or discolouration of the fingers or toes Dangerous symptoms: Difficulty breathing or shortness of breath Chest pain or pressure Loss of ability to speak or move Seek immediate medical attention if you have serious symptoms. Always contact a doctor or health facility before heading to it. People with mild symptoms should treat their symptoms at home, even if they are otherwise healthy. It takes an average of 5-6 days for symptoms to appear since a person becomes infected with the virus, but it can take up to 14 days for symptoms to appear.</string>
    <string name="prevention">To help prevent the spread of COVID-19: Wash your hands often. Use soap and water or an alcohol solution to sterilize your hands. Keep a safe distance from anyone who is coughing or sneezing. Wear a muzzle when physical distancing is not possible. Do not touch your eyes, nose, or mouth. Make sure to cover your nose and mouth with your elbow or tissue when coughing or sneezing. Stay home if you feel sick. Seek medical attention if you have a fever, cough, and trouble breathing. You should contact your health care provider before you go to him so he can quickly direct you to the appropriate care facility. This will protect you and prevent the spread of viruses and other diseases. Gags Masks can help prevent transmission of the virus from the person who wears the muzzle to others. However, masks alone do not protect against infection with Covid-19, but physical distancing and hand hygiene must also be observed. Follow the directions provided by your local health authorities.</string>
</resources>
